你想借此表现一下?
You want to make a statement?
- 你想像个真正的黑帮 伙计? - 当然
- You want to gangsta up, homie? - Yeah
你得勇敢点 对吗? 经典双动左轮
You got to go bold, all right? Double action old school
质高 简练 精准 从不卡壳 来吧 试试看
It's sweet, it's simple, accurate never jams Here we go, give it a try
- 冲哪儿打? - 不知道--要不直接射那管子吧
- Where? - I don't know- just-just shoot the pipe
射的不错
Nice shot
你还有什么货?
What else you got?
行 我手上还有这好兄弟
All right, got the homie's best friend here, all right?
九毫米口径 贝瑞塔 意大利出品
It's a nine mill, it's Beretta it's Italian
十五发子弹加上枪管里的一发
All right, it's 15 plus one in the snout
我建议上些空尖弹
I'll throw in a box of hollow point hot loads
放心 不会有任何问题?
Trust me, your stuff will be safe, okay?
来吧
Here, here we go
这枪真劲爆!
Bad boy is tight!
你还没看到最劲爆的呢
You ain't seen the baddest boy yet, all right?
造物主的恩赐 能让大地震动
Sweet mother of God The pagans shall quake
这是Tech 9 本系列最好的
It's a Tech 9 It's top of the line
全自动
Fully automatic
四秒钟就能打光一个弹夹的子弹
You can empty the clip in four seconds flat
- 你够男人用这个吗? - 当然
- Are you man enough for this? - Yeah
- 真的? - 真的
- Yeah? - Yeah
好 试试看 试射一次
Yeah, all right, give it a shot, give it a ride
- 喜欢吗? - 当然
- You like that? - Yeah
- 伙计 你看上去高大威猛许多了 - 当然!
- You're looking taller already, buddy - Yeah!
我们他妈赶紧跑! 快走! 快走!
Let's get the hell out of here! Let's go! Let's go!
-=伊甸园美剧http://sfile.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 衡在头 灰色隐蔽 猪在尾 校对: 米兰的猫 时间轴: 咔肉肉
NCIS 第六季 第15集 有恩必报 720P.WEB-DL校对:CrazyTorrent
丢了东西 麦可爱?
Miss anything, McLovin?
这个 一个叫Melinda的女人找你 她得延后了
Just this It's from a woman named Melinda She had to postpone
延后什么?
Postpone what?
不知道 以为一说你就明白了
I don't know Figured that you'd figure it out
她的情绪如何?
How did she sound?
我问问题 你回答 她的情绪如何?
I ask the question, you give the answer How did she sound?
- 我不知道 Tony - 你不知道
- I don't know, Tony - You don't know
要么试试用你的那些怪词形容 宝石麦先生?
Well, why don't you try using your words, Mr Gem City?
气急败坏的? 沮丧万分的?
Devastated? Despondent?
兴高采烈的
Delighted
好吧 她的电话是多少 麦龟毛?
All right What's her number, McDetail?
她没留
She didn't leave one
惯例就是要留名字 电话和完整信息
It's customary to get a name, a number and a complete message
这不是完整信息 这是一团糟
This is not a complete message This is a complete mess
Melinda
你那本子上有多少个Melinda?
How many Melindas do you have in that thing?
不知道 说不定是健身房里 跟我聊天的那个姑娘
I don't know It could have been the girl I talked to at the gym
你才不去健身房
You don't go to the gym
也许是遛狗公园里我搭讪的那个
Maybe it was the girl I talked to at the dog park
你可没养狗
You don't have a dog
噢 有可能是我约会对象去洗手间时 我在电影院零食摊碰到的姑娘
Oh, it could have been that girl I met at the concession stand
While my date was in the bathroom
你得要个私人秘书了
You need a secretary
或者心理医生
Or a therapist
或两者都要
Or both
自由高地那边有枪击事件 准备出发
Shots fired in Liberty Heights Saddle it up
如果自由高地每次有枪击 他们都要跟我们打电话...
If we were called every time shots were fired at Liberty Heights
华盛顿警局先出动 他们找到了个陆战队员尸体
Yeah, Well, Metro responded They found a dead Marine
受害者是一等兵Emilio Salazar
Victim is Private First Class Emilio Salazar
四个月前加入陆战队
Joined the Marines four months ago
下周将会被派遣
Scheduled for deployment next week
Ducky?
交通堵塞 二十分钟后应该能到
Stuck in traffic Should be here in about 20 minutes
九毫米弹壳 可能是两把枪
Nine millimeter shells Possibly two guns
参考那面墙上的弹孔深度 我猜另一把是点357
And based on the level of penetration on that wall
I would say 357
没有弹壳 所以应该是左轮
No shells, which means a revolver
一名枪手 三把武器
One shooter, three weapons
有两套脚印
There's two sets of footprints
枪手身边可能有个观察员
Shooter could have had a spotter
- 或望风的 - 或目击者
- Or a lookout - Or a witness
嘿 DiNozzo
Hey, DiNozzo
McGee
新的陆战队规定不允许暴露在外的文身
New Marine regulations don't allow for exposed ink
他把文身去掉了 激光去除的
He had his tat removed, laser
看上去像是-- "P..."
Looks like- "P "
看上去像那个
It looks like this
PCS
我去问问华盛顿警局的黑帮调查科
All right, I'll check with Metro's gang unit
子弹射穿了天窗...
Bullets hit the skylight
杀了我们的陆战队员
killing our Marine
让他来了个很短的蹦极跳
Sending him on a very short bungee plunge
但为什么要从这里射杀人质?
But why shoot your hostage from down here?
也许他们是想传达一个讯息
Maybe they were sending a message
McGee的那种--模棱两可 无法破译
The kind McGee takes- cryptic, hard to decipher
血迹
Blood
这血迹已经干了
This blood is dried
但警局那边不到一小时前 才收到枪击报案电话
But Metro made their "shots fired" call less than an hour ago
看来谜团更神秘了
Looks like the West just got a bit wilder
手铐 老大
Cuffs, boss
皮肤 血迹...
Skin, blood
这人被捆在这儿挺久的
This guy was strapped up here for a while
所以我才喜欢皮毛制手铐
That's why prefer the fur handcuffs
不是啦 老大 是给我女伴的
Not really, boss That's for her
我不带手铐的
I don't wear the cuffs
有人想要传递讯息
Someone was trying to send a message
用鲜血写的
Written in blood
电话号码?
Phone number?
不是电话号码
Not a phone number
不知道"G"代表什么 但有九个数字
I don't know what the "G" stands for, but it's nine digits
可能是军队里的服役号码 我来查
Could be a military service number I'll run it
不用了
You don't have to
是我的
It's mine
他人呢?
Where is he?
我不太清楚 主任
Um, I'm not exactly sure, Director
告诉他我要见他
Tell him I need to see him
我会向他转达的
I will give him the message
以及这个讯息的内容
And the nature of the message
包括是谁说的 电话是多少
I'll include who it's from, and the number
为什么有人会把Gibbs的陆战队服役编号 留在楼顶的案发现场?
Why would anyone leave Gibbs' Marine service number on a rooftop crime scene
Gibbs探员的办公桌
Agent Gibbs' desk
不 他不在
No, he's not here
但我很乐意帮您留个详细的讯息
But I'd be happy to take a detailed message
飞机2:30到达
Flight arrives at 2:30
能留个名字和回电号码吗?
Can I take a name or a return number?
好 我会的
Oh, okay I will
名字和号码
A name and a number
够了 行不? 我明白了
Enough, okay? I understand
我很抱歉 但你要我怎么样?
I am sorry, but what do you want me to do?
难道去查今早总机接通的来电数据库
You want me to sort through the database
Of every call that came into the switchboard this morning
And match incoming call to your desk phone using a date and a time stamp?
然后用时间标记对比打到你桌上的电话?
对 那样就再好不过了 谢谢
Yeah, actually That'd be great Thanks
嘿 老大 你有两条讯息 呃实际上 就在那儿 抱歉
Oh, hey, boss, got two messages for you, actually, right there Sorry
Vance主任要你尽快回电 然后另一个是...
Director Vance wants you to call him back ASAP, and the, uh
另一个是... 那里
the other is, uh And then there's-there's that one
说飞机2:30到 是M街旅行社的
Um, it says that the flight arrives at 2:30 It's from M Street Travel
我猜是个旅行社吧
I assume that's a travel agent
没说飞机起飞的地点和乘客名字
Didn't say where the flight was from or who the passenger was
如果你想告诉我们 别担心...
But if you want to share that, you can feel
死者情况?
Dead Marine?
一等兵Emilio Salazar 服役记录
PFC Emilio Salazar Service record
十八岁 两月前在帕里斯岛 完成基础训练
18-year-old Completed basic training at Parris Island two months ago
驻扎在匡迪科
And was stationed at Quantico
还有更多资料
Had more than a service record
犯罪纪录可以追溯到2003年 Emilio才12岁
Criminal record goes back to 2003, when Emilio was 12
都是少年犯罪纪录 跟黑帮有关的
All juvenile offenses All gang-related
帮派文身
Gang tattoos
原罪
Or Pecados Capitales
原鱼?
Capital Fish?
致死的罪孽 白痴 鱼的西班牙语是pescado
Deadly Sins, you idiot Fish is pescado
干嘛嘲笑我
Don't scoff at me
很多黑帮都以致命的鱼类命名的
Lots of gangs are named after deadly fish
有鲨鱼 梭鱼...
There's the Sharks, there's the Barracudas
斗鱼
Rumble Fish
这个帮派也被称为PC
These guys are also known as the PCs
听上去很像你的风格呢 麦主板
Sounds like your kind of gang, McMotherboard
这孩子混了六年帮派都活了下来 当了四个月的陆战队员就死了
Kid lives through six years in a gang can't survive four months as a Marine
也许有人不想他脱离帮派?
Maybe someone didn't want him to leave the gang?
也许是以前仇家杀了他?
Maybe a rival gang killed him?
但那解释不了你的军队服役编号 老大
Though that wouldn't explain your service number, boss
专心追踪杀手
Focus on tracking the killer
那另一个可能在现场的人呢?
And what about the other person who may have been held there?
去找枪手
Find the shooter
Vance要你尽快回电给他 老大
Vance wanted to call him ASAP, boss
你第一次说的时候我就听到了 DiNozzo
Heard you the first time, DiNozzo
Jackson下士 扣动扳机时不要闭眼!
Private Jackson, do not shut your eyes when you squeeze the trigger!
别朝着那些玩具流口水 David 我们不是来玩的
Eyes off the toys, David We didn't come here to play
我好多天没来射击场了
I have not been to the range in days
在射击场请勿喧哗
No talking on the range, please
那就麻烦了 Medina上士 因为我很喋喋不休...
Well, that's going to be a real problem, Staff Sergeant Medina
'Cause I'm real talky and I have a badge
而且我还有警徽
有地方能让我们谈谈的吗?
Is there somewhere we can talk?
停火! 停火! 退出子弹推上保险! 待命!
Cease fire! Cease fire! Clear and lock 'em! Stand by!
谢谢你们
Thank you
你队里一名士兵昨晚遇害了
A man in your unit was killed last night
- 怎么回事? - 枪战 他输了
- How'd it happen? - Firefight He lost
- 有人开枪射他 - 多次
- Someone shot him? - Several times
知道是谁干的吗?
You know who did it?
我们要知道就不会来找你了
If we did, we would not be here
想到也许你能帮上忙
Thought you could help
乐意效劳
Any way I can
他在从小长大的街区被害
He was killed in the neighborhood where he grew up
他谈到过自己的过去吗? 帮派 麻烦?
He ever talk about his past? Gangs, trouble?
他一直都在谈这些 想要逃离那一切
All the time He was trying to escape it
那么你知道他参军前有犯罪纪录咯?
So you knew he had a record before he joined the Marines?
有些孩子成长的环境 比他们将要去的沙漠地区危险得多
Some of these kids grew up in a jungle
A lot more dangerous than the desert we're sending them to, you know?
Salazar ever drop names, gang affiliations, enemies?
Salazar提过些名字 帮派联系人 或者敌人吗?
没有什么具体的
Nothing specific
他和其他所有混帮派的孩子一样有些麻烦 但没提过具体人名
He had troubles like any kid who runs in gang circles
But he didn't name anybody
如果你想到了什么 联系我
If you can think of anything, let me know
- 贝瑞塔-- 九毫米 - 随便用
- Berettas- nine millimeter - Feel free
- 你介不介意我试试? - 没问题 长官
- Do you mind? - Not at all, ma'am
尽你所能
Do your best
噢 老天
Oh, God
待命 2号射击位 开枪!
Stand by, station two, for live fire!
我更喜欢SIG一些
I prefer the SIG
很多女枪手不太喜欢贝瑞塔
A lot of women have trouble with the Beretta
后坐力太强
Thing's got too much of a kick
你的准星歪了几毫米
Your sight is a few millimeters off
- 真的? - 真的
- Really? - Really
在一等兵Salazar死亡前 手铐造成了这些擦痕和伤口
Prior to PFC Salazar's demise
Handcuffs made these abrasions and lacerations
是啊 但他没被扣多久
Yeah, well, he wasn't held there long
的确没有 几乎一被锁住就遇害了
No He was executed almost immediately upon his confinement
- 至于死亡原因... - 枪击
- As to the cause of death- - Gunshots
呃 是 也不是
Well, yes and no
这些伤口是机枪造成的
These wounds were made by machine-gun fire
间隔太对称 不太像是随机扫射的
The spacing is too symmetrical for random shooting
另外 也没有红印淤痕之类的
Also, they showed no signs of redness or braiding and bruising,
说明他被机枪射中之前就 已经死了
indicating that our private was long dead when he was strafed
死了多久?
How long?
根据肝温判断 六个小时
About six hours based on his liver temperature
在这里...
And here
单一弹孔 九毫米 刺穿了心室
single round, nine millimeter punctured the pericardial sac,
造成心肌梗塞
causing a cardiac tamponade
他饱受折磨Jethro... 也许持续了二十到三十分钟...
He suffered greatly, Jethro- perhaps for 20 or 30 minutes-
他并没有立刻死亡
and he did not die quickly
杀死他的那颗子弹呢?
The bullet that killed him?
在万能的Abby Sciuto手上
In the capable hands of Abby Sciuto
你以前从未在我到达案发现场前 就离开现场的 Jethro
You've never left a scene of a crime before I arrived until this one, Jethro
是啊 有别的事要做
Yeah Had something else to do
跟你的陆战队服役编号有关的?
Something to do with your Marine Corps service number?
我自己也在好奇这个
I was wondering the same thing myself
你在逃避我
You're avoiding me
我忙着侦破一宗谋杀 Leon
I've been busy solving a murder, Leon
我有线索了会第一个让你知道
When I have something, you'll be the first to know
我需要查阅一份陆战队资料
I'm looking for a Marine file
机密资料
A classified one
最高机密 仅供阅读
Top secret, eyes only
黑色行动
Black Ops
炮兵军士长 Leroy Jethro Gibbs
Gunnery Sergeant Leroy Jethro Gibbs
下次要是有客人 菜鸟 记得在屋里留点苏格兰威士忌
Next time you having guests, probie have some scotch in the house
这次没能用甜言蜜语让空乘给你点?
Ah, you couldn't sweet-talk the flight attendant
Out a few of those little bottles?
- He wasn't my type - Right
- 我对男人没兴趣 - 好吧
什么事这么急?
What's so urgent?
你把我从孙女身边拉过来
You pulled me away from my granddaughter
刚刚才庆祝她的两周岁生日呢
Just celebrated her second birthday
我要找个人
I'm looking for somebody
Rose
Vance知道我来了吗?
Vance know I'm here yet?
还没
Not yet
也许我该借条领带
Maybe I should borrow a tie
哥伦比亚是很久以前的事情了 军士
Colombia was a long time ago, gunny
只有一个人知道她的事情
Only one person knew about her
你
You
18年是很久以前了 菜鸟
18 years is a long time, probie
但她今天就在华盛顿
She's in DCToday
Mike
你想要我说什么?
What do you want me to say?
说出你隐瞒的事实
Whatever you're not saying
你怎么能肯定她在此地?
Well, how do you know she's here, for sure?
我的陆战队服役编号被留在 命案现场楼顶
My Marine service number was written on the roof of a crime scene
用血写的
In blood
可能是任何人留的
That could have been anybody
我特意加了个G在服役编号末尾 只告诉她一个人
I put a "G" on the end of it, just for her
17年前我把她带到这里
I brought her here 17 years ago
她现在在哪儿?
Where is she now?
我把她安顿好后就再也没见过她了
I haven't seen her since the day I dropped her off
那我们就从那里找起
Let's start there
你就把她扔在这儿?
You put her here?
那时候这地方可没这么糟
Wasn't such a hellhole then
你们好
Que paso?
风景不错
Que es lo que miras?
我要找Rose Tamayo
I'm looking for Rose Tamayo
妈 有人在门外
Ma, alguien esta a la puerta
是谁?
Que se les ofrece?
Rosa Tamayo在家吗?
Buscando Rosa Tamayo?
她十年前就去世了
Ella se murio hace diez años
我们来得晚了点
We're a little late
她十年前就去世了
She died ten years ago
估计有其他人知道了 你的海军服役编号 菜鸟
Guess somebody else knows your Marine service number, probie
嘿吼 Leon
Howdy, Leon
Mike
他有目前一个案子的相关资料
He has information on a current case
我需要他的帮助
And I need his help
谢谢你搞定那个抚恤金的问题 Leon
Thanks for sorting out that little pension problem, Leon
十分感谢
Appreciate it
我会竭尽所能帮助任何一位 前任探员的 Mike
I didn't do anything I wouldn't have done for any former agent, Mike
都是按规矩办事
All by the book
当然 按规矩
Absolutely By the book
这就是我们现在的操作方法
That's how we operate now
这也是最合适的方法 Leon
Wouldn't have it any other way, Leon
他注意到我领带没有?
Think he noticed my tie?
有何收获?
What do we got?
我们已经控制了这地区 但没人愿意开口
We canvassed the area No one is talking
- 这是smurf war(电脑攻击术语) - 应该是地盘争夺战
- There is a smurf war - Turf war
两个互相争斗的帮派 PCs和绿色狂魔
between two competing gangs, the PCs and the Verde Psychos
弹道
Ballistics
我们将子弹和杀死Salazar一等兵 的枪做了比对
We matched the slug that killed PFC Salazar to a gun
这枪在两周前一起未破的抢劫案中 曾经被使用
that was used in an unsolved robbery two weeks ago And
警方首要嫌疑犯是Victor Carmado 又称大力水手
Metro's chief suspect is Victor Carmado, a k a Popeye
Victor Carmado在PCs里 声望很高
Victor Carmado is a known member of the PCs
他今天带着团伙在自由高地那转悠
He was hanging out with his posse at Liberty Heights today
DiNozzo Ziva 带他进来
DiNozzo, Ziva, bring him in
Abby!
- 嘿吼 亲爱的! - Franks! 你在这干什么?
- Howdy, darling! - Franks! What are you doing here?
菜鸟觉得我在这能帮上忙 我只是找个理由来看望你
Probie thinks I'm here helping him, but it was just an excuse to come see you
Abs 关小声点
Abs, turn it down
多酷啊
This is so cool
有人在房顶写下了你的服役号码 然后你就突然出现了
Someone writes your service number on a roof, and then you just show up
就像有人发出求救信号 蝙蝠侠立即现身
It's like sending out the bat signal and having Batman just show up
还有他的良师益友 拉萨格尔 (蝙蝠侠最厉害的敌人)
And his mentor, Ra's al Ghul
或是像蕾拉公主发送全息图
Or-or like Princess Lela sending a hologram
"救救我 欧比万"(星球大战)
"Help me, Obi-Wan "
然后欧比万和他的师傅魁刚金 就出发去营救
And then getting Obi-Wan with his mentor, Qui-Gon Jinn
真诡异 这两个导师都是 Liam Neeson扮演的
You know, it's weird 'cause Liam Neeson played both the mentors
那你说我为什么来这?
You gonna tell me why I'm here?
我化验了用血写的服役编号
Oh, um, I ran the blood from the service number
和死者Emilio Salazar不吻合
It does not match our dead Marine, Emilio Salazar
我早知道了
I already know that
可不是吗
Of course you do
我希望 你不知道这血是属于 另一个陆战队员的
Well, hopefully it'll be news to you
That the blood did belong to another Marine
一等兵Tomas Tamayo
Private First Class Tomas Tamayo
就你表情来看 这个你不知道
Judging by the look on your face, that is news to you
他和一等兵Salazar来自同一街区
Um, he comes from the same neighborhood as PFC Salazar
据记录 十年前从哥伦比亚移民来后，他母亲就去世了
According to his records
His mother died ten years ago after emigrating from Colombia
Rose有个儿子?
Rose had a son?
是的 我带她来这时 他才一岁
Uh, yeah He was about a year old when I brought her here
你知道这事?
You knew?
我猜你不知道
I'm guessing you didn't
我需要个地址 Abs
I need an address, Abs
金斯顿街57号
57 Kensington Street
房主是一个叫Maggie Scott的女人
The home belongs to a woman named Maggie Scott
菜鸟 这事可急不得
Might want to take this slow, probie
结果可能不是你想看到的
Might not like where it leads you
大力水手Carmado? 我们是NCIS
Popeye Carmado? NCIS
我们在听同一首歌吗?
Are we all listening to the same song?
让我猜猜 里奇马丁的粉丝
Let me guess Ricky Martin fans
"Livin' La Vida Loca"
"Livin' La Vida Loca "
伙计 你最好离开
You ought to leave, man
可我们刚来这
But we just got here
但这附近很危险
Yeah But this is a very dangerous neighborhood
所以我带她当保镖
That's why I brought her
这小妞是个联邦探员
La Bonita es una federale
身手最好的一个
Federales saben buenas
这小妞会狠狠的揍你
La Bonita will kick your ass
没错吧?
Is that right?
你知道吗 这周围总出事 美女
You know, bad things happen in this place, mamita
但仍然感觉是个家
But it's so homey, homey
我喜欢你墙上的涂鸦
I love what you've done with the wall here
"史努比爱小妞?"
"Snoopy loves Chiquita?"
你们哪个睡狗屋 哪个是小妞?
Which one of you sleeps on a doghouse and which one's a bana?
我猜这是你们的秘密没错吧?
I'm guessing the love is between you two Am I wrong?
你觉得他们想玩石头剪子布吗?
Think they want to play rock, paper, scissors?
- 你搞定他们了? - 搞定了
- You got them? - I've got them
怎么了? 大力水手今早没吃菠菜?
What's the matter? Popeye didn't eat his spinach this morning?
Rico! Chuy!
Rico Suave九十年代很红 Chewie和千年隼一起复出
Rico Suave's stuck in the '90s, and Chewie's back with theMillennium Falcon
让我们看看小妞做的怎样
Let's go see how La Bonitadid
你怎么这么久?
What took you so long?
McGee!
你干吗呢? 为什么要查NCIS数据库?
What are you doing? Why are you digging through the NCIS database?
这女人打电话给Tony 我没她号码
This woman called for Tony, and I didn't get the number
号码是屏蔽状态 所以我想试着定位追踪一下...
It was blocked by the carrier, so I am trying to coordinate a trace
别忙乎了 这事更重要
Well, drop the call This is much more important
好的 什么事?
Okay, what's up?
我听到了些东西
I heard something
不是全部 只是一部分
Not a complete something, a partial something
但足以让我觉得这事有蹊跷
But enough of something to make me think it means something
所以我要知道你是否 知道一些那些东西
So I need to know if there's any other something that you know about?
什么 我 我没听明白
What- I'm-I'm lost
好的 是关于Gibbs
Okay It's something about Gibbs
和哥伦比亚 还有个叫Rose的女人
And Colombia And a woman named Rose
还有十八年前她的一个儿子
And a son she had 18 years ago
那是在1991年 Gibbs加入NCIS之前
That would been 1991- before Gibbs joined NCIS
快点 McGee
Come on, McGee
在什么上搜索点关于什么的什么啊
Type something about the something into something
没防守 他没防守
Open, he's open
把球给我
Give me the ball
踢啊
Shoot it
脚法不错 女士
Nice shooting, lady
在这周围总练习
Get a lot of practice around here
你是Maggie Scott?
You Maggie Scott?
嘿 Henry 进来 好吗?
Hey, Henry, come in for me, okay?
发生什么事了? 你们是警察?
What happened? You guys Metro?
NCIS
谁被袭击了? 这个街区的人?
Who got hit? Somebody from this block?
我知道这是Thomas Tamayo的家
I understand this is the home of Thomas Tamayo
为什么? 他没事吧?
Why? Is he all right?
他被卷入一场谋杀
He was involved in a murder
我的天啊
Oh, my God
不 他不是受害者
No, he wasn't the victim
受害者来自旁边那条街
Someone a couple of streets over
Emilio Salazar
Emilio 是的 他是Tomas的朋友
Emilio Yeah, he's a, uh, he's a friend of Tomas's
他母亲 有人和Emilio母亲联系过吗?
His mother, has anyone contacted Emilio's mother?
正在联络 Tomas在哪?
Being done now Where is Tomas?
他在休假 海特岬 之前在阿富汗
He's on leave, Cape Hatteras Before Afghanistan
不对 昨晚他在华盛顿 的一个犯罪现场
Wrong He was at a crime scene last night in DC
等一下
Hold on
你是他的法定监护人?
You were his legal guardian?
很多这种孩子的法定监护人
Legal guardian to a lot of these kids
让他们做守法公民
Keeps them out of the system
他们母亲下班之前都由我照看
I just watch them till their moms get home from work
他们大多没有父亲
Most of them don't have fathers
几个月前两个孩子失去了手足
Two of them lost siblings, past couple months
战争?
War?
帮派火拼
Gang war
你不是来自这附近 对吗?
You're not from around here, are you?
大学后我搬过来的 是Vista计划的一部分
I moved here after college Part of the Vista program
我从未离开这里
I never left
你如何成为Thomas的监护人?
How'd you become Thomas's guardian?
Tomas12年前搬到这里
Tomas moved in about 12 years back
那时Rose病倒了 是癌症
Then when Rose got sick- his mother has cancer-
她求我照顾他
she asked me to look after him
他是个好孩子 很好的孩子
He's a good kid He's a really good kid
我的天 太好了 他来了
Oh, my God, It's okay He's here
是Tomas 那是Tomas
It's Tomas It's Tomas
Tomas!
- 你没事吧? - 很好啊 怎么了?
- Are you all right? - I'm fine What is this?
我很担心你
I was so worried about you
这是怎么回事?
What's going on?
你想告诉我过去48小时你在哪里吗?
You want to tell us where you been for the past 48 hours?
和朋友在海特岬
Cape Hatteras with friends
我们查过了
We checked
你手机打出的电话都来自 华盛顿的两个街区
Your cell calls were all made from a two-block area of DC
你为什么被关在这?
Why were you being held here?
我没有
I wasn't
我的军队服役编号
My military service number
房顶有你的血迹
Your blood on the roof
你引起我的注意了Thomas 我就在这 你想要什么?
You got my attention, Thomas I'm here What do you want?
那不是我
It wasn't me
训练中我把自己弄伤了
I cut myself traing
Gibbs和那孩子
Gibbs and the kid
房顶就是你那该死的血
It was your damn blood on the roof
- 有什么关联吗? - 我们测试了
- What's the connection? - We tested it
为什么他受伤了?
And why the kid gloves?
嘿 让我出去!
Hey, let me out!
我们来自街区的朋友
Our friend from the hood
- 他冷静的够久了吧? - 让我出去 伙计!
- Think he's chilled long enough? - Let me out of here, man!
是时候让他开口了
Time to unpop his cork
快让我出去!
Let me out of here!
冷静点 小子! 别对着墙撒气
Cool it, Coolio! No gangbanging on the walls
坐下
Sit down
- 我才不坐下呢 - 坐下!
- I ain't sitting down - Sientate!
或者你想让小妞帮你坐下?
Or do you want La Bonita to sit your ass down?
我以为你们忘了我在这 就这些
I thought you all forgot about me, that's all
你着急去什么地方吗 大力水手?
You in a hurry to get somewhere, Popeye?
因为短期内你都别想见到 奥利佛和小甜豆了
'Cause you sure ain't going home to Olive Oyl and Sweet Pea any time soon
你要蹲大牢
You're going to prison
谁说的?
Says who?
一等兵Emilio Salazar体内的 九毫米子弹说的
Says the nine-millimeter slug we pulled out of PFC Emilio Salazar
与你之前参与的另一起枪击案吻合
Matches the slug from another shooting you were involved in
要是有目击证人 我早被关押了
If witnesses put me there, I'd have been locked up already
我们有个死掉的陆战队员 曾是你的团伙成员
We have a dead Marine, former gang member of yours
这是凶器
This is the murder weapon
被扔在一个泄洪道 认出没有?
Found dumped in a storm drain Recognize it?
就它? 你们就这点证据?
That's it? That's all you got?
我们只需要这些
It's all we need
这只是间接证据
It's all circumstantial
我认为你们什么证据也没有
I think you got nothing
我觉得你们需要的是我的认罪词
I think what you need is a confession
作为谋杀陆战队员的从犯 你面临十年的牢狱
You are looking at ten years for accessory to a murder of a USMarine
如果我们证明你是主犯 就更不止十年
More if we tag you for murder one
房顶有你的汗迹
Your sweat was on that roof
房顶有你的小便
Your pee was on that roof
还有你的血迹
Your blood was on that roof
不打算说说房顶发生过什么事吗?
You gonna tell us what happened on that roof?
你最好说谁还在那里
You're gonna tell us who else was there
谁开枪杀了一等兵Salazar
Who put that bullet in PFC Salazar
我们推测就是你
We're gonna have to assume it was you
我没杀Emilio
I didn't kill Emilio
- 谁干的? - 我
- Who did? - Me
我杀了那混蛋
I killed the little bitch
你杀了一等兵Salazar?
You killed PFC Salazar?
是的 我干的 你抓到我了
Yeah, I did it You got me
那蠢货早就该死
The fool deserved to die
究竟怎么回事 Victor?
How'd it go down, Victor?
我向他开枪 就是这样
I shot him That's how it went down
用枪指着他脑袋 啪
Put the gun to his head- pow
打得脑浆迸裂
Blew his brains out
你向他头部开枪?
You shot him in the head?
灯灭了 伙计
Lights out, baby
肯尼迪式谋杀
JFK style
左边靠后 明白我说什么吗?
Back and to the left, know what I'm saying?
胸口一枪
One shot to the chest
就是这样杀了你朋友Emilio
That's what killed your friend Emilio
他没立即咽气 过了好久
But he didn't die right away It took time
大约20分钟
Maybe 20 minutes
子弹打穿心脏
Bullet nicked his heart
血涌入他的肺中
Blood poured into his lungs
- 记得吗 Tomas? - 不
- Remember, Tomas? - No
他呼吸困难
He would have had trouble breathing
一定是痛苦难当
The pain must have been excruciating
- 你知道这一切 不是吗 士兵? - 我不在场
But you know all this don't you, Marine?
I wasn't there
大力水手没对他开枪
Popeye didn't pop the guy
那样的小孩撂不倒两个陆战队员
No way a kid like that took down two Marines
街头斗殴可能提高了他的水平
Probably taking credit for a street kill to elevate his stature
一等兵Tamayo那有收获吗?
Get anything on PFC Tamayo?
- 他很害怕 - 他有所隐瞒
- He's scared - He's hiding something
他们两个都是
They both are
这事还另有门道
Something more going on than that
说的没错 菜鸟
You're right, probie
帮派分子不会绑架敌人
Gangbangers don't kidnap their enemies
他们直接将敌人击毙街头
They shoot them in the street
有人背后操纵 命令开枪
Somebody's pulling strings, calling shots
我想我知道是谁
I think I know who
我反复核对警方反黑组名单中 PC成员的名字
I've been crosschecking the Metro Gang Task Force's list of known PC members
来对比以他们名字登记的手机号码
against cell numbers registered in their names
有个号码反复出现
One common phone number keeps popping up
这是街区外的一个号码 和PC的所有成员都通过话
It's a number from outside the neighborhood
That called almost every member of the PC gang
他就是射击场的那个上士
That's the COfrom the shooting range
Vicente Medina上士
Staff sergeant Vicente Medina
并不完全 我看了上士过去的资料
That's not all I looked into the staff sergeant's history
看来不止是电话记录有共同之处
It seems he shares a bit more than phone records in common
他不仅曾参加过PC
He wasn't just recruiting from the PCs
他曾经是成员之一
He was a member
把他带来
Get him in here
- 是 Gibbs - 在我办公室见
- Yeah, Gibbs - Meet you in my office
我这就过去
I'll be right there
- 陆战队资料 - 是你的
- Marine file - It's yours
我还没看呢 如果你不愿意 我就不看
I haven't read it yet, and I won't if you'd prefer I didn't
我想它也许能告诉我18年前在 哥伦比亚发生了什么...
I thought it might shed some light on what the hell happened in Colombia
18 years ago unless you'd prefer to
除非你想让我看
我没啥好遮遮掩掩的 Leon
I got nothing to hide, Leon
每个人都有自己的秘密
Everybody's got something to hide
Franks也参与此事了?
Franks a part of this?
一点点
A little part
好东西都在最后5页里
Some good stuff in the last five pages
你杀了多少人?
How many men have you killed?
确认的有7人
Seven confirmed
在哪儿?
Where?
安巴尔3人 法卢加2人 巴格达1人 塔拉博拉 1人
Three in Anbar, two in Fallouja, one in Baghdad, one in Tora Bora
那华盛顿特区呢？
How about Washington, DC?
从没有
None
你认识Emilio Salazar?
You knew Emilio Salazar?
他是野战排长 长官
His platoon sergeant, sir
他和你一样是帮派成员
He's a gang member just like you are
那都是很久前的事儿了
That was a long time ago
就在昨晚!
That was last night!
长官 我没有杀那个陆战队员!
Sir, I did not kill that Marine!
那你昨晚干嘛来着?
Whatwereyou doing last night?
我在家看电视
I was at home watching TV
有谁能证明你在看电视?
Anybody watching you watching TV?
没有
No
你家距离案发现场只有20分钟的路程
Your place is 20 minutes from our crime scene
电话记录单
Phone records
你过去的六个月和半数的PC成员联系了
You made contact with half the PC posse over the past six months
你的警方记录
Rap sheet; yours
PC长达三年的头目
Shot caller for the PCs for three years
一朝陆战队员 终身陆战队员
Once a Marine, always a Marine
一朝进PC 终身PC人
Or once a PC, always a PC
这就是我的生活 又不是啥秘密
I lived the life It's not a secret
我喜欢这样 直到看到我的朋友们身上发生的事 不是进监狱就是在17岁就挂了
I liked it, till I saw what was happening to my friends
In dead or jail by 17 so I joined the Marine Corps
所以我加入了陆战队
成为一个好人
Made me a better person came back to the hood
回来找到他们并试着说服他? 让他们为自己想想
And tried to convince others to make something of themselves
在系统里进行了面目识别搜索
Ran a system-wide facial recognition search
我想你愿意立马看到结果
I thought you'd want to see this right away
好 我们从头再来一遍 昨晚你在哪里?
Okay, let's try this again Where were you last night?
我...我说了我在家
I... I told you I was at home
巴尔的摩!这是昨晚的录到的!
Baltimore! That was taken last night!
你不可能杀他
You couldn't have killed him
那为什么要说谎?
Why are you lying?
我是想去看看儿子
I went to visit my son
当时我15岁 犯了个愚蠢的错误
When I was 15, I made some mistakes
我让一个女孩怀孕了 而我妻子...
I got a girl pregnant And my wife
她不知道我有一个孩子
she doesn't know I have a kid
我认为我们在白费力气
I know what we got; nothing
我们找错方向了 是吧？菜鸟?
Guess we all make mistakes, huh, probie?
两个陆战队员被"栓"在同一屋顶上 不知道原因
Got two Marines chained to a roof Don't know why
有人在后面操纵此事 不知道是谁
Got somebody behind it pulling strings Don't know who
如果我们能逆转时光 就能找出Gibbs在哥伦比亚干了什么?
Can we wind the clock back to the part
Where we find out what Gibbs was doing in Colombia?
Or how it is connected to the gang?
或者和黑帮有啥联系?
找到个承认杀人的阿飞 却是清白的
Got a punk who didn't kill anybody who says he did,
那个写下菜鸟服役编号的孩子 却说自己什么也没做
and a kid who wrote probie's service number in blood saying he didn't
你们好了么?
You done?
好看着你用黄油刀刮脸
Done watching you shave with a butter knife
让我同那小子谈
Let me talk to that kid
我会让他说出到底他妈的发生了什么
I'll get him to tell us what the hell's going on here
我不能让你那样做 Mike 我放他走了
I can't do that, Mike I let him go
你..啥?
You what?
如果你想挖掘点啥 跟上
If you want to find something, you follow it
我可是跟你学的
I learned that one from you
你们俩...
You two
- 和McGee呆在MTAC里 - 明白 老大
- MTAC with McGee - Got it, boss
以为我不知道你在干嘛？
Think I don't know what you're doing?
试图为那小子开脱?
Trying to get that boy off?
对 还能领我们找到真相
Yeah, gonna lead us to the truth
真相
The truth
对 一个17年前你就该告诉我的真相
Yeah, which you should have told me 17 years ago
当我带 Rose离开哥伦比亚 你正在享受第二次婚姻
When I got Rose out of Colombia, you were happily married again
- 或者我以为你很享受 - 真相到底是什么?
- Or so I thought - What's the truth?
真相就是 她不想你知道!
The truth is, she didn't want you to know!
她知道你在Shannon和Kelly的事后 还没有完全走出来
She knew you were still putting the pieces back together
After Shannon and Kelly
不想打乱你的生活
Didn't want to complicate your life
我想她终究没有如愿以偿
Guess she didn't get her wish after all
或许Gibbs当时参加的是秘密镇压藤森 集团的行动（前秘鲁总统 被控犯有屠杀平民罪）
Maybe Gibbs was on a covert mission to suppress the Fujimori coup
那个是在秘鲁 不是哥伦比亚
That was Peru, not Colombia
好的老大 我们还在监视放在一等兵 Tamayo手机上的卫星定位器
Okay, boss, we're still following the GPS signal from PFC Tamayo's cell phone
他正往匡提科方向 离那里约20分钟车程
He drove to Quantico He's been there about 20 minutes
匡提科在那个方向 菜鸟
Quantico's that way, probie
我们不去匡提科 那是他始发站 我们去他的终点站
We're not going to Quantico That's his first stop We're going to his last
就像那我女士说的 Mike "战争爆发"
Like the lady said, Mike "It's a war "
他降落在哥伦比亚的波哥大
So he's down in Colombia in Bogota
他挽救了比尔 克林顿总统的生命
He saves President Clinton's life,
可是不许向任何人提起 因为是个超级秘密
but nobody can talk about it because it's super secret
克林顿93年才开始任职
Clinton did not serve until '93
别八卦了!
Stop obsessing!
我不是八卦 我是小有执着
I'm not obsessing! I'm a little preoccupied
我或许稍有考据控 但我不是八卦
I'm a tad fascinated by the whole subject, but I amnot obsessing
17年前他到底在哥伦比亚干什么啊?
What was he doing in Colombia 17 years ago?
18年前 而且是机密 DiNozzo
18 years ago- and it's classified, DiNozzo
那个也是机密？ 或者可以和你的主任分享分享？
Is that classified, too, or can you share with your director?
我们 呃... 在为Gibbs追踪嫌犯 主任
We're, uh, tracking a suspect for Gibbs, Director
Franks和他在一起？
Franks is with him?
一猜一个准
That's what I thought
定位器显示一等兵Tamayo 刚刚离开匡提科
PFC Tamayo's just left Quantico
他现在正往自由高地方向行驶
He's now headed towards Liberty Heights
呃 您想让我们干怎么做?
So, what do you want us to do?
继续你们刚才在做的工作
Whatever you were doing before I walked in
Tamayo在匡提科的岗位是啥?
What's Tamayo's duty assignment at Quantico?
军械库的警卫
Guard duty at the base armory
那个被谋杀的陆战队员呢?
And the dead Marine?
一等兵Salazar也是军械库的警卫
PFC Salazar was also a guard at the armory
也就是他们都有进入军械库的密码
Means they both had access to the armory codes
我往后 抱歉
Stepping back Excuse me
- 给基地安全部打电话 - 遵命 长官
- Get base security on the phone - Yes, sir
如果那孩子开枪你会还击 对吧?
Hey, if this kid starts shooting you're gonna shoot back, right?
现在真的不是时候 Leon
This is a really bad time, Leon
我刚刚挂了和匡提科军械中心的电话
I just got off the phone with the Armory OICat Quantico
丢了四箱M-4冲锋枪
Four crates of M-4 assault rifles are missing
那是你的一等兵Tamayo干的 Gibbs
That's your PFC Tamayo, Gibbs
黑帮 军火 总是相伴相随
Gangs, guns It adds up
我们还在监控他的卫星定位
We're still monitoring his GPS
- 他回去是找他的目标 - 目标
- He's headed back toward the projects - The projects?
对 我们找到他了
Yeah, we got him, we got him
我按照你说的做了 行了吧?
I did what you wanted, okay?
不 你听我说!
No, you listen to me!
你想要 就过来拿
You want 'em, you come get 'em
第二层...我等着
Second floor- I'm waiting
这下真的有意思多了 菜鸟
This is about to get real interesting, probie
McGee 大街对面的大楼
McGee, building across the street
交通监控头 在阿什顿大街3837号
Traffic camera, 3837 Ashton
- 找到了 - 录下来
- Got it - Record it
开始录了
Recording
你一个人 兄弟?
You alone, homes?
放大这几个小子的脸
Zoom in on those guys
里面 那俩
In Those two
这不是那俩人么?
Aren't those the two guys?
Chuy和Rico 我应该多给他们 点颜色看看的
Chuy and Rico I should have hit them harder
你拿到了?
You got 'em?
别动!别动!举起手来!举起手来
Freeze! Freeze! Freeze! Put your hands in the air! Put your hands in the air!
你以为可以用海军的枪 来杀我的朋友们么?
You thought you were gonna use Marine guns to kill my friends?
有点不对劲
Something's going down
有人在他后面
Somebody's behind him
McGee 拉远点看 拉远点
McGee, zoom out, zoom out
不 到此为止!
No! This ends here!
这TM的咋回事?
What the hell?
别动 上士
Don't move, Sergeant
DiNozzo 呼叫救护车和后援
DiNozzo, call for an ambulance and backup
不管你走到哪儿 小子 都有人中枪
Everywhere you go, kid, somebody gets shot
阿什顿大街3832号发生枪击 多人受伤...
3832 Ashton shots fired Possible multiple casualties
用力压住这里 上士
Keep pressure on it, Sergeant
嘿 Leon
Hey, Leon
让我和他说
Let me talk to him
他正忙 要带口信么?
He's busy Can I take a message?
你刚刚开枪打死了人 Franks
You just shot somebody, Franks
对 完全照章办事 Leon.
Yeah All by the book, Leon
退休探员涉及枪击
Retired-agent- involved shooting
是不会公开的 对吧?
That's still a form KJ-65, right?
- 很高兴和你聊天 Leon. - Fra...
- Nice talking to you, Leon - Fra
是我
It was me
我命令他把武器带出基地 带到这里给他们的
I ordered him to take those weapons off the base
And bring 'em here like they wanted
为什么?
Why?
- 因为我是... - 不 不是你 是你
- Because I was - No, not you You
他们把我困在屋顶
They held me on the roof
说如果我不把武器给他们 他们就会伤害我的家人
Said they'd hurt everyone I love unless I got them the assault weapons
我...我不相信
I... I didn't believe them
他们以前都是我的朋友
They used to be my friends
然后他们就威胁Emilio
Then they threatened Emilio
在我面前给了他一枪
Shot him in front of me
我以为他们也会杀了我
I thought they were gonna kill me, too
所以你把我的服役编号写下来?
That why you wrote my service number?
当我知道你就是NCIS的时候 我想告诉你的 但...
When I found out you were NCIS, I wanted to tell you, but
我命令他不许说
I ordered him not to
为什么?
Why?
企图用军队的枪来伤害街区的孩子 那些我想要拯救的孩子 这让我气坏了
Using Marine guns to kill kids in my hood
Kids I was trying to save it made me sick
我想自己解决
I wanted to handle it myself
我们自己照顾自己
We take care of our own
这些家伙都是受雇于人
Those guys are just the hired help
- 这就是你要说的? - 对
- That is all you have to say? - Yes
是我做的 我承认 我会给你们一份完整的认罪词
I did it, I admit it I'll give you a full confession
我可以跟他说话吗?
Can I talk to him?
不 他会被送去监狱
No, he's going to prison
求求你 我...
Please, I
他从海军基地偷武器给街头帮派
He stole weapons from a Marine base to arm a street gang
有人因此死了
People died
他承认了一切
He confessed to everything
所有一切 都是他的主意
All of it, his idea
所以他咎由自取
And he's going away
除非你有什么话想说
Unless you've got something to say
等等 他什么也没做 他在说谎
Wait He didn't do anything He's lying
等等
Hold up
没人该受伤的
Nobody was supposed to get hurt
他们只应该恐吓一下 这样Tomas和Emilio就会去帮PC偷枪了
They were supposed to scare them so that Tomas or Emilio would get the guns
Emilio不应该中枪的
For the PC's Emilio wasn't supposed to get shot
这都是意外 我发誓
That was an accident, I swear
是谁想要武器 Maggie?
Who need weapons, Maggie?
我们的孩子们
Our kids
整个街区 我们的街区
In the neighborhood, on our block
每天都有人被打死
They were getting killed every day
被毒贩和帮派杀死
Slaughtered by drug dealers and bigger gangs
每天都有人死去!
They are dying every day!
我要保护他们
I had to protect them
用什么? 把他们用突击步枪武装起来?
By what, arming them with assault rifles?
我在冷战中长大
I grew up in the Cold War
我父亲跟我说过威慑力量...
My dad talked about deterrence-
如果你建立了自己的兵械库来抵制敌人 他们便不会再来攻击你
if you build up an arsenal that rivals your enemy's, they won't attack you
你明白吗?
You understand?
结案了...我的结案了 你的还得继续
Case closed- my case, and you being on it
Melinda 555-0199
"Melinda 555-0199"
等一下 我知道这个号码
Hold the phone, Malone, I know that number
你应该知道...这是你牙医办公室号码
You should- it's your dentist's office
他们重新安排了你的预约
They rescheduled your appointment
哦 那个Melinda
Ooh, thatMelinda
长着一双男人的手
The one with the man hands
我希望你学到了一课 菜鸟
Well, I hope you learned a lesson, probie
对...永远不要帮你接电话
Yeah- never to pick up your phone again
等一下
Wait a second
真相一直在我眼前
It was right in front of me the whole time
Franks! 我有个问题问你
Franks! I've got a question for you
要赶飞机
Got a plane to catch
18年前 在哥伦比亚
18 years ago, Colombia
Gibbs在那里进行扫毒活动
Gibbs was doing drug interdiction down there
Tomas18岁 来自哥伦比亚
Tomas is 18, from Colombia
知道Gibbs的海军陆战服役号码
Knows Gibbs's Marine service number
问题是?
Question?
Gibbs是Tomas的父亲吗?
Is Gibbs Tomas's father?
告诉菜鸟...多谢借我领带
Tell probie thanks for the lend
坐下吧 随便点
No Sit down As you were
你的令状
Your orders
去阿富汗
Shipping out to Afghanistan
我...我不用坐牢?
I... I'm not going to jail?
你帮助调查案子
You helped the investigation
我妈妈曾经跟我讲过一个 陆战队员的故事
My mother used to tell me this story about a Marine
他经常来我们村里帮忙
He came to help out our village
但是毒贩跟踪了他...
But the drug cartel came after him
朝他开枪 他奄奄一息
shot him He almost died
她救了他 帮他疗伤
She hid him, helped him heal
那就是你
That was you
而当你痊愈以后...
And when you finally got well
你告诉她如果她需要任何帮助
you told her that if she ever need any help,
就对任何陆战队员亮出这个编号 你就会来找她
she could give that number to any Marine and you would find her
她让我背下了这个号码
She made me memorize that number
你就是我加入陆战队的原因
You're the reason I became a Marine
当年你母亲救我的时候 她已经怀着你了
When your mother saved my life, she was already pregnant with you
大多数人 他们从没有第二次机会
Most people, they don't get a second chance
祝你好运
Good luck
永远忠诚
Semper Fi
Ooh-rah
看过了在哥伦比亚贩毒组织中 抓获Cesar Castillo的任务报告
Read about the mission to eliminate Cesar Castillo
From the Cali Cartel in Colombia
看得怎样?
Good read?
让人印象深刻
It was impressive
1200码以外击中目标心脏
Took out your target with one shot to the heart from 1, 200 yards
这个Castillo只是小意思
This Castillo was a piece of work
毒贩 侩子手 强奸犯
Drug dealer, torturer, rapist
我只是做本分
I did my job
如果你没有受伤 任务就会悄无声息的结束
And the mission would've gone off without a hitch
If you hadn't been wounded
我想你全部赶上进度了 Leon
Well, I guess you're all caught up now, Leon
帮助救了你命的女人的儿子 一定让你感到很复杂吧
Must've been poignant helping out the son of the woman that saved your life
你有没有告诉那个孩子 是你杀了他的父亲?
Did you tell the boy that the man you killed was his father?
-=伊甸园美剧http://sfile.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 衡在头 灰色在中间 猪在尾 校对: 猫在一边 时间轴: 咔肉肉